Hey, that's your target right over there.
The Tycoon, Mr. Batera.
What am I watching?
Well, the Greed Island video game, of course.
But what makes you so interested in a video game, sir?
You've spent a considerable amount of money on it already.
The answer, my dear, is love.
When you fall in love with something, you want it all to yourself.
Love? Really? There are so many rumors flying around. Would you like to make a comment?
I'm gonna get my hands on the clue, Jean left.
どうもいい?
Am I right?
You can fly away
So I slept for half a day
Well, more like two days, buddy
Where's the boss? And what about the auction?
Oh, uh, they cancelled it completely
The rest of the merchandise will be sold online
The boss accepted that
Don't lie to me
The boss was really looking forward to taking part in the auction
I don't see her accepting that so easily
The troop murdered Skuala
And Elisa
Well, she was inconsolable
The Scarlet Eyes we won were stolen
But apparently
The boss was more upset over Elisa's state than the loss of her prized possession
That was when she informed us she wanted to go home
I understand
Kouan and Killua
They're both just fine
And right now?
He's out
Rest up
Your friends are doing what they have to
So you don't have to worry about a thing, okay?
Our next item is the fabled game
Known as Greed Island
And it has a mysterious power
Let's take a look
Now as I'm sure all of you can plainly see
A mysterious power protects the console from any damage
Well, as long as someone is playing inside the game, that is
This man is Jade Sari
He's the player who's inside the game even as we speak
As a matter of fact
He's the one who signed a contract allowing us to auction it off
So Jean didn't bring this one here
Jade Sari left behind the following contract that stipulates
If no one has cleared the game by the contract date
Even if he and the seven other players are still inside the game
He would consign all seven units of the game
As well as the consoles
To the Southern Peace Auction
And entrust his dream of clearing the game to other challengers
Unfortunately, when we received these units
The game had ended for two players
Losing the game results in actual death for a player
This dangerous game requires that you risk your own life
Only bid if you're prepared for the consequences
The starting bid is 900 million, Jenny!
I have 1 billion!
1.5!
Number 105 doubles it!
71 doubles again to 6 billion!
Crap!
My big brother!
So you use your hand to tell her how much you want to bid?
Yeah, the auctioneer looks at the crowd's hand signals
To discern the highest bid instantly
Number 16 doubles it again to 12 billion!
What's this mean?
201 doubles it again to 24 billion!
You idiot!
Number 16 bids 25 billion!
That was a close one
Okay, so I'm guessing he wasn't able to decipher that memory card
I have 25.5 billion!
How much money does he have?
Number 16 raises to 30.5 billion!
30 and a half, is that right?
It's of no consequence
Or at least it won't be as long as we're able to clear the game
Excuse us, but the two of us are hunters
We're willing to offer our help in clearing Greed Island
That's real funny
Now why don't you two run along?
We're not joking!
I really am a professional hunter!
Sure you are
I assume you have a hunter's license
Yes, sir!
It's at the pawn shop, remember?
I don't have it on me
What a surprise!
I knew he was lying!
No, I'm not!
Just hold on a moment
The fact you're here at the auction in the first place
Tells me you're no ordinary children
However, I can't take your word at face value
I am looking to hire professional hunters
In order to clear this game, that much is true
But I'm afraid I simply can't hire either of you at this time
Because there's a limit to the number of players you see
Not good
Did we fail already?
I'm thinking we don't actually need to buy the game
Not if we just want the data inside it
And I bet there are probably going to be some people who win Great Island
Who are going to look for other people to play it for them
The number of players is limited?
Each memory card only has the capacity to store one player's data
With multi-taps, you can have a maximum of 8 players per console
Hey, he's right!
Remember?
That Great Island save used up all 30 blocks on that memory card
Yeah
How did you know?
We got a Great Island save file a little while back
So we figured it out
What about the game itself?
Have you played it?
No
We only have a memory card
Wait
Does that mean...
If the memory card you speak of is real
You would still need another item
In order to remove the card from the console
You think maybe...
He means the ring
They know about the ring, too?
It appears that these two boys may be worthy of our consideration
I assume you know Nen
Let's have a demonstration of your Ren
Okay
What do you think?
Hopeless, I'm afraid
Hiring them would be a complete waste
They would simply run around in circles until they died
How do you know when we haven't even tried?
It'd be too late by then, you see
Better to die quick than squeak by
You would only be delaying the inevitable
See, as long as a player is alive inside the game
You can't reset
Nor can you remove the memory card
In other words, it's impossible to send in new players
I've personally hired around a hundred professional and amateur hunters to play this game
And just over half of them have already given up
What do you mean?
They've given up on ever returning to the real world
Choosing instead to live their lives inside the game
That's why I'm so careful selecting players
We need people strong enough to obtain items
And then return them safely to the real world
So of course we have to be much more selective
Are you trying to imply that we're not strong enough?
Yeah
Why does that guy think we can't do it?
Because he is a professional hunter
And one who has played Greed Island before
Speaking from my own ample experience
The items we wish to bring here are easy to obtain
With your paltry nen, it's hopeless
As a matter of fact, it'd be game over for you in no time
Once the screening is complete, I'll be returning to the game
Wait, you're gonna be screening players while you're here?
That's right
Starting on the final day of the auction
So if you're planning to participate
I would recommend putting some additional work into your nen
We were gonna do that anyway
Come on, let's go
Before you leave
How did you come to have a memory card?
I'm not telling
Damn it
Those jerks
We've definitely got to pass their screening now
Screening, huh?
So what's the plan?
Do you even need to ask?
We are bandits
We steal, of course
Well, let's go back to the hideout and play it
A memory card is already inserted
Which means only one more person can play
We'll use a multi-tap
Four more can play now
Very nice
So, who's gonna go in first?
I will
He's really gone
I didn't think that would actually happen
What was that?
It's a game
You guys wanna play?
I pass
Maybe a little later
Fine
I'll catch you later then
He disappeared too
It's a game, right?
What kind?
It says right here
That it's one where you can actually die
It's listed in the catalog for the auction
Hmm
I can't believe he treated us
Like we're just dirt
Damn it
I know
But you've gotta admit that he's got a point
What do you mean?
Just chill out a little
Look
We should start thinking about taking all this to the next level
What are you talking about?
Hatsu
I mean our special attacks
Huh?
Think about it
Kurapika started learning Nen the same time we did
But because of his special attack
He was able to take on the Phantom Troop
Yeah
With the powers that he obtained
He basically became invincible against them
By placing his life on the line
We can't limit ourselves
We need special attacks that fit our specialties
And that can minimize the risk
Something practical and effective
That's what we need to come up with
I figured this would happen
Let's take one step at a time
First off, what kind of abilities do you want to have?
That's a good question
Well
Hey
You must have an idea at least, don't you?
A really strong one
Be more specific, man
To start with
Think about something that's in your own category
You're an enhancer, right?
Try to think of a power that enhances something
Okay
Then think about
What part you want to strengthen
And exactly how you want to do it
Hey, that hurt!
What ability do you want then?
I already know
And that's why I'm trying to help you out right now
Really?
What is it?
It's a secret
Gon
I'm gonna go practice my special attack now
And you keep thinking about yours, okay?
If you don't
I might be the only one who passes the screening
If I don't put a little fear in him
Chances are he's only gonna get distracted
Visualize my aura
Infused with electricity
Then visualize discharging the stored electricity
While refining my Nen
With your paltry Nen
It'd be game over for you in no time
Damn that guy!
I'll show him game over!
I see you're hard at work
Kurabika!
Feeling any better?
Yeah
My fever broke
So
I'm alright now
Wow
He sure doesn't look alright
But
If Kurabika finds out that the spiders are still in York New City
Will there be any way to stop him?
Tell me
How did everything go at the auction?
I believe you were going after an expensive game?
Uh
Yeah
I see
So they're screening players, are they?
Hey
What kind of training did you do while you were gone?
Once I decided I wanted to conjure chains
Mostly imagery training
Not only did I feel them with my eyes closed
I drew hundreds, maybe thousands of sketches
I looked at chains and even tasted them
Smelled and listened
My master told me to play with them constantly
So that's exactly what I did
After a while, he took them away from me
And it was then that I began to hallucinate chains
It wasn't long after that
The hallucinations felt heavy
I could feel them, cold and grating
And once that happened
I was able to conjure chains myself
But otherwise, it was the same as you
Just Ten and Ren
Kay
I've got an idea
You can be my master
You can point out what I'm doing right
And what I've got wrong
This way, I can keep Kura pickup busy
While the auction happens
I'm sorry, but I can't
What?
I'm afraid that my boss will be leaving tomorrow
And I'm obligated to accompany her
You're leaving York New?
Yes
Although I'm still concerned about the spiders
But it has been two days now
So I suppose they probably left already
Well, it's probably for the best
But what about you?
Who taught you, Nen?
You should ask them
They'd be a better resource than I am
A special attack
That's just like you two
I can tell you this much
Enhancers really don't need a special attack at all
But why not?
Well, because enhancers are the most balanced
Both in offense and defense
If you can master Ten and Ren
You will produce enough force
To be quite destructive indeed
What if I don't have that much time?
The screening's just four days away
Gon
If I were a judge
I would be very disappointed
If someone showed me
An improvised special attack
Now listen carefully
No matter what happens
You must not try to emulate Kurapika
If you think about it
I'm sure you won't need me to tell you why
No, sir
So, just be yourself
You're powerful enough on your own merits
That you really have no need to imitate others
You think so?
I do
I want you to reflect on each of the things
That you're capable of
If you do
You'll find the answer you're looking for
I need a hint
Please
Just a little one
You're starting to sound a little bit desperate
Haste makes waste
But hard work always pays off
Yeah, I agree with you
But if it wasn't for this deadline
All right, then here's a hint
When you demonstrated your power
For this Tsesgara person
It was just your normal Ren, right?
Yeah
Next time, show him everything at the same time
Everything, sir?
Yes
Pay attention, Gon
Show him everything you've learned
At the same time
Everything I've learned at the same time
Ten
Contain the aura leaking out of the body
Zetsu
Shut off the aura by closing the nodes
Ren
Bring forth an incredible amount of aura
And Hatsu
Wait
Ren is bringing forth my aura
But Zetsu is suppressing it
If I do both at once
Did his brain short out again?
Get it together, Gon
If you take too long
I'll leave you behind
How am I supposed to summon something
And suppress it at the same time?
I want you to reflect on each of the things that you're capable of
After Mr. Wing helped unleash my nen
I got seriously hurt in battle
Because all I really knew how to do was ten
But I mastered Zetsu in the process
Then I learned Gyo
So I could see through Hisoka's special ability
Gyo
Oh yeah
I still have Gyo
Gyo
Focus aura in your eyes
So you can see hidden aura
Focus?
That's right
I was so focused on my eyes
That I never thought about trying to put aura anywhere else
There's a little aura being released
If I can suppress the rest
I can do them all at once
I did it!
It's no use
The second I relax
It falls apart
But it's possible
If I can just focus all the aura built up through Ren
How much power could I have?
I want to see
I have to try it out!
Haste makes waste, Gon
Os!
Sounds like a breakthrough
But you're still not gonna beat me!
The two boys are about to undergo a brand new awakening
目指す
朝日に照らされたキス
笑い張って
終わることない旅を
続けよう
向かい風としていながら
それでも進む理由がある
だからと思よ
置いてくためだけに生きるのはまだ
早いだろ
身につけたもの
破壊込んだもの
手放したとき
始まる何か
うまく生きてく
レシピを破り捨てて
感じるリズム
そう、僕らのやり方で
Coming up! The Great Island Tutorial!
YouTube
それがノイデア Of my face
を點てくる
busy
サクンディング
セミナング
the
テレビ
リラ
どっかい
お
怒り
という